[music]
Hi guys,
hello guys.
Welcome back to our YouTube channel.
After yesterday, there were probably a lot of
wedding events and we also uploaded a lot of
videos of our wedding, now we are
vlogging and we are going on a honeymoon
trip.  Yeah.
Now where are we, darling?
We're in Soul, we're in Korea.
From Korea, of course.
So actually this was a
sudden planning.  We have bought tickets from
[music] Jakarta to Rome.
It turned out that I suddenly had a job
offer and I felt that this was a
good opportunity.
So my husband gave in and let us
leave Sou.  So he really
arrived at Soul this morning
because El had to stay for
Dad's birthday.
So, he ended up only being in Korea for
half a day.
How do we start from the sale soul reading?  Our soul sale
is at Incan airport, we are
waiting for
boarding.  Now we want to go to
Dubai road transit now.
We are so excited.  How long will we have,
darling?  Mil almost 3 weeks plus
yes almost 3 weeks.
Yes, just keep following it.  Bye
bye.  [music]
Yey,
why is it closed?
Hello.  Finally
he gu on the plane.
We
go to Dubai and we go to R Street and
then we go on holiday.  Anyone?
Let's go.
Let's go.  [music]
Good morning.
Morning.
H
is trying to adjust the time to
Yes because it's still 6 am at home
[music]
hah finally finally
arrived at the row
I swear guys,
how long did we queue for migration, honey, the
hours are more Jang is even crazier, the queue is
really long and it's hot.  Oh my God.
Our city room while staying here for 2
nights, right?  tonight we moved around
now we have someone waiting for
us with Kak Diko again who
accompanied us
and today we also don't know
what the plan is.  We want to go to the hotel first to
clean up, then we want to look for
dinner tonight and we don't know what we want,
okay, let's go.
Bye.  [music]
[music]
until we arrived in Italy, we bought it
and then we found out
where we were going to go today.
[music]
How are you, honey?  Tired, huh?
Huh?  After not spending the night in Korea,
then coming here, the flight took a total of 20
hours including transit, and when I got here it was
hot so I wanted to take a shower.
Okay, let's take a shower first, guys,
and then we can get some sleep tonight [music]
.
Okay.
Hello, Guys.  We guys
day one.  We want to go for a walk at the Trates
Fair.  Where are we going to eat?
Want to eat at Trfere?
And this is also there.  Let's go.
Hello.  We ended up wanting to eat at
one of the famous eating places in
Restere as expected.  The prayer time is
really long and it's drizzling all the time,
guys.
It's like we're queuing in the
rain, right, Beb?   There is
no canopy,
it is a struggle
just for this food.  It's a good thing
my hair is in a bun today, I
swear.
For example, if it's done, it's a bit of a hassle.
OK guys, let's do it
on the inside.  Hi guys, so now
we are inside the restaurant.
We also ate the appetizer earlier.
What's the name of it?  Fokasia bread only.
Yes.  We are now waiting for the main
course.  It is said that Syifa's
most famous word is what is it called?
Carbonara carbonara and this cheese pizza,
basically I admit that I
cooked all of them because he was good at
TikToking.
I'm trying the other one,
the pasta is like tomato paste and
we'll try it,
which one is delicious, what's the difference?
This one is tomato. There, I
finally feel like eating pasta.  I've always
only eaten pasta in Indonesia.  This
in the cage is like eating shrimp and pete
but in Indonesia.  This is
pasan no.
Uh, for dessert there is Tiramis.
Tiramisu.  So, our two favorites.
Our two favorites, baby.
Let's try.
Very close together.
Uh, very
Oh, very this yes.
Wow, look guys.  So, the
Transveri area is famous for its
many lights at night.
[music]
Very nice.
Hi guys.
Hi guys, we're back.
This is our second day in the room.
Yes.  Yesterday we only had time for dinner and a
walk around
Tres TV.
Yes.  Now today we want to
go around the room.
Yeah.  The Vatican wants to go to Kalsum.
Colsum.  Terus e Travy fountain.
Fun.
Later, if we have more time, we will
explore the others.  But
today we are so excited about those three places.
Yeah.  Yesterday we were
so knocked out [gasp] we
really got to the room and were completely knocked out.
Because the time difference between Korea and
Indonesia is greater.
I'm really pissed off guys.  I'm so excited.
The journey was tiring.  So, stay tuned,
Guys.  [music]
[music]
Hi, Guys.  We arrived at the Vatican, the
smallest country in the world.
This is the smallest country because the
country is in a
room.
We are exploring the
Vatican.
After visiting Vatican City, we
strolled around the area.  In
front of there is San Angelo Castle.
Okay, guys.  So, we are going to
Pon and Travah.  Earlier we were from the
Vatican and Angelo Castel.
Wow,
this pantheon is
n't even a pantheon yet, but it's already pretty cool
.  Pantheon indeed.
[music]
Now we're going to eat.  This is one of the ones
on my list too which I say is
delicious.  But that's what it's called.
Here, someone makes the pasta right in
front of you.
There's cheese here.
Then
I ordered this ravioli.   It's
really bad.  Rabbits eat it, guys.
Try.
Yeah.  Another tiramisu.  Anyway,
tiramisu.  Anyway, wherever we
eat, the dessert has to be
tiramisu.
We will try which tiramisu is the
most delicious.
But it's not as delicious but not as
delicious as the bar
but this is also very delicious in my opinion.
It's just a different type.  If yesterday it was
really liquid, then yesterday it was liquid and there
was a pit inside it.
Okay, Guys.  So, this is
really good.  But yeah, you can't take
a photo because you can see so many people
.  So even if you take a photo, the
background is mostly people.
But at least we've seen it
directly.
[music]
Hi guys, we are now at the
Tring Coliseum.  Wow.
We are at the landmark of Italy.
Yes, it's the place where the Gladiators used to
compete.  Now we are
here.
If in the past there were Gladiators, now
there are Elrumi
fighting.  [laughs]
Finally we get to the landmark.
We actually went through this yesterday
too, but we didn't stop.
Iyaar- hotel.  But now
we want to take pictures here and the
weather is really nice.  The wind is strong
.  I think it's pretty cool for
me.   Cool
.  Cool, cool, cool.  But it's quite
cold.
Yeah.  On the streets around the Colosseum
and photos
and photos.  This is the person who took our photo
holding the camera.  [laughs]
Coincidentally, Brother Niko was picking up the car
so we were accompanied by Brother Ilham
this afternoon.  Warlock.   The
weather is lacking, Sis, right?  Sir,
today it was Windy again.  Eh, Windy is
back again with Claudi, so
who are Windy and Claudi?  So
where else do you want to go, Masel?
Now from the Colosseum because it seems
the weather is not very supportive, the light is not
very supportive but we also have a lot of
time here.  What museum were we going to go
to earlier?
To the altar of Del Patria.  National museum.
Altar of the Fatherland.
National Museum of Italy.  And the view there is also
nice.  Since yesterday, we went to
Musum and only took photos outside.
[laughs]
Next time we do.  Yes  Absolutely.
Because we only dropped by for 2 nights, we did
n't have time to explore
the museums one by one.  So let's just stay
outside for now, later we'll
come and see.
Yes
Let's go.  We're going there.
There.
We are exploring the Colosseum area.
Have to go back home to
explore one by one because
from here now we are only here in size.
Look
from afar.  But
I really like it.  But if
I'm honest, I'm curious, like I want to go
inside.
Yes  Then I also like history so I
want to
get to know more.
Later we might go to Rome again but
we will study the history first so we
understand it better but now at least we have
seen the words are good.
[music]
Hey guys, so it's 2338
and it's almost Els birthday.  We were
hanging out on the rooftop of our hotel
while waiting for 12.00.  I just
asked Kadiko for a small cake.  So,
oh my god.  So excited today, eh, I
'm eh, it's almost 12 o'clock. Tomorrow,
I mean, I'm preparing a surprise
dinner at our hotel in Tas Keni
in Borgo Santo Pietro.  So
tomorrow we will move to this task.  Well, I've
prepared a surprise sunset dinner for L.
So, I'm really excited.  Eh, honestly I'm
really nervous.  I really arranged to
make the moodboard and this is the
outdoor surprise for the dinner.  So,
I really hope it's not cloudy,
I hope it doesn't rain.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.  Now I
want to take the cake first and make it upstairs, as a
surprise, that's the story.
Okay, I'm with the cake.
We just have to wait about 15 minutes
more before I go up to the
rooftop and give this to L. Okay,
just a minute, T. Guys, honestly I'm confused about
how to open the door.
Nobody wants to go up here anymore
.   I
swear I forgot how to open the door
.  This can't be opened.
Huh?
Honestly, it's odd.
Wait a minute, guys.  We are looking for [music]
happy birthday
to you.
Happy birthday to you.  Happy birthday
baby.
Happy birthday.
I was locked outside earlier.  I don't
know how to get in.
Happy birthday.
Still how about
the small surprise.  [music]
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
Make a wish.
Make a wish.  Make a wish.
Look at the one next to me.  U deh.
Yeah.
Happy birthday.
Love you.
How does it feel to be 27 years old?
Happy, glad.  So now you're at your
first birthday and you're married, right?  Previously, I was
not married for 26 years.
And now at this new age,
what do you hope for?  Hey.
May you have a
happy, blessed little family and may
your family members be added to.  Absorbed.
Amen.
And basically, I'm really happy to have my
birthday abroad with
my darling, my wife,
you,
and what else?  Anyway, I'm really happy.
Thanks for the little surprise.
Equally love.
Thanks.  Love you so much.
Love you.
Thank you.
Yes  [sigh][gasp]
Yeay!  Thank you for the surprise.
Everyone, what's your wish for me?
My wish is that the baby will always be happy with
me.
Amen.  Amen.
The more blessed you are, the more protected you are by
Allah, the smoother
your affairs will be.
Amen.
Become a better person
even though you are already very good now.
God willing,
hopefully we can be together in this
world and the hereafter.
Amen.
Love you.
Thank you for the surprise.
Today we move on to bags.
Yeah.  See you tomorrow today,
okay?   It's
already 12 o'clock today. Oh,
bye.